I fucking hate Ben Bruno because every couple months he sends me some insane
looking exercise that obviously I have to try and when I do they're really
freaking difficult but they're also really freaking good so then I get
pissed that I didn't think of it first. This is one of those exercises. Ben calls
it the pigeon iron cross and as crazy as it looks think about what you're
getting here. You're strengthening your entire upper back while simultaneously
stretching the shit out of your glute. So basically Ben figured out a way to
combine two things that almost every guy needs more of upper back strength and
hip mobility. In the video Ben texted me he was using 25 pound dumbbells for 10
second sets but I decided to start lighter with 12 pound dumbbells although
I was able to hold them for 45 seconds. So now I'm challenging all of you. Give
this exercise a shot tag me and Ben and let us know how much weight you used and
how long you lasted. Good luck. I fucking hate.